<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<rss version='2.0' xmlns:atom='http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom'>
<channel>
<atom:link href='http://sercanulucan.com/daily' rel='self' type='application/rss+xml'/>
<title>
Sercan Ulucan
</title>
<link>
http://sercanulucan.com/daily
</link>
<description>
daily posts about anything
</description>
<lastBuildDate>
Sun, 03 Jan 2016 16:03:32 +0200
</lastBuildDate>
<generator>
clj-rss
</generator>
<item>
<guid>
http://sercanulucan.com/daily/daily/posts/2016-01-02.html
</guid>
<link>
http://sercanulucan.com/daily/daily/posts/2016-01-02.html
</link>
<title>
RMK Museum
</title>
<description>
&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/daily/img/20160102_rkm.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt tag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the greatest musuem to visit in Istabul is &lt;a href='http://www.rmk-museum.org.tr/en/index.htm'&gt;RMK Museum&lt;/a&gt;. There are many unique and well prepared items and collections from different places of the world. The main categories are Mustafa Kemal Atatürk, road transport with wonderful cars, rail transport with real locomotives, navigation with a submarine, aviation with both military and civil planes, machinery, communication, scientific devices, models and toys, and the exhibitions was about Dolls Houses. It would take more than one day to observe every item in detail. The cafes in the museum were pretty good and cheap, thus, it's possible to have a rest during the exhausting day. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/134530188@N05/albums/72157660751378324&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is an album of the pieces from my camera. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<enclosure>

</enclosure>
<pubDate>
Sat, 02 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0200
</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<guid>
http://sercanulucan.com/daily/daily/posts/2015-12-27.html
</guid>
<link>
http://sercanulucan.com/daily/daily/posts/2015-12-27.html
</link>
<title>
Zero Art Movement
</title>
<description>
&lt;p&gt; &lt;img src=&quot;/daily/img/20151227_zero.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;alt tag&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It's an interesting coincidence that my first post is about &lt;a href='https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zero_(art&amp;#41;'&gt;Zero&lt;/a&gt;, the art movement raised after second world war to initialize a new beginning. Actually, I have similar feelings for my life and career with the idea of this art, thus, it was an fascinating activity to see the prominent pieces at &lt;a href='http://www.sakipsabancimuzesi.org/en'&gt;Sabancı Museum&lt;/a&gt;. In addition, it was interesting to see how artists used vibration, light, space, soot, nail, and other metarials to express their feelings. Although the movement is extremely modern, abstract, and too hard to understand, I enjoyed visiting the museum accompanied with a guide. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.flickr.com/photos/134530188@N05/albums/72157662247203840/with/23380385513/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Here&lt;/a&gt; is an album of the pieces from my camera. &lt;/p&gt;
</description>
<enclosure>

</enclosure>
<pubDate>
Sun, 27 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0200
</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
